Finding Aid for the Ralph Story Papers LSC.0867
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 1. Broadcasting -- Radio and Television
  - Television, Serial Programs, 1959 - 1982
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.228 - 231, 1969 March 23 - 1969 April 13 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      No.228 Olga girdles; Jim Dannaldson, Batman. 1969 March 23. no. 229 missing from collection no.230 MOS Cure for hiccups; Thomas Keyser, abandoned cars; sanctuary. 1969 April 6. no.231 MOS school song; subways; flags. 1969 April 13.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.232 - 235, 1969 April 20 - 1969 May 11 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      No.232 MOS takeout food; Griffith Park Zoo; baseball. 1969 April 20. no.233 Garment industry. 1969 April 27. no.234 Backyard boats; MOS which side of the bed. 1969 May 4. no.235 MOS Chief Reddin; camels; egg cartons. 1969 May 11.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.236 - 240, 1969 May 18 - 1969 June 22 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      No.236 La Cienega; Hamilton High school. 1969 May 18. no.237 Hollywood Bowl. 1969 May 25. no.238 Dirt. 1969 June 8. no.239 MOS places never visited; Santa Anita; ventriloquist. 1969 June 15. no.240 Street sweeping; rubber castle. 1969 June 22.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.241 - 245, 1969 June 29 - 1969 November 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      No.241 Jeffries bank note; window washing. 1969 June 29. no.242 MOS salesmen; women's shoes. 1969 July 13. no.243 MOS ways to waste time; swans, Bel Air Hotel; civil servants. 1969 July 27. no. 244 missing from collection. No.245 Pollution in ocean and hard times for independent fishermen; Frank Bonelli, county supervisor and artist. 1969 November 2.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.246 - 248, 1969 November 9 - 1969 November 23 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      No.246 Columbia Records' vinyl record factory; roller-skating jobs; Lunar Archeological Society. 1969 November 9. no.247 artificial lakes; water Waiters boat delivery service; MOS resemblance to famous people. 1969 November 16. no.248 Lockheed P-38 fighter planes. 1969 November 23.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- film sign-in sheet, 1963 December 14 - 1969 November 23 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles --letter and record from James Bruce Joseph Sievers, who appears in unknown episode, 1981 July 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Ralph Story Los Angeles research clippings, 1977 - 1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - KNXT/CBS proposal for late night show about movies and movie-making, research and proposal, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Show proposal Story Time, undated, but after RSLA (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Story's Thing -- pilot for CBS, scripts, correspondence, expenditures, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - "Now and Then" pilot -- script note cards, 1969 - 1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Ralph Story's America pitch, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- research, press kit for "The Hiding Place" by World Wide Pictures, Billy Graham's production company, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- research on Dinah Shore, 1975 May (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Includes 14 photographs (8x10 inch black and white) publicity stills of Dinah Shore with guests on her program
    - ABC News -- AM America -- correspondence and kudos, 1974 - 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- sales presentation, 1970 April (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- log of titles and airdates, 1971 - 1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- Thirty Minutes Over Hollywood (tour), 1971 September 16 (script) and October 3 (air) (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- The Subject Was Noses, 1971 September 29 - October 10 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- Madame X-tra (film extras), 1971 September 29 - October 17 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- Catch a Falling Star (stuntwomen), 1971 October 8 - 31 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- Road to Carefree (Bob Hope location), 1971 October 20 - November 7 and 1972 January 2 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- Howard Hughes is Alive and Well and Living in Hollywood, 1971 November 5 - 14 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- The Gates of Wrath (gatecrashers) and Write On (autograph collectors), 1971 November 21 and December 26 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- Flora! Flora! Flora! (greenery) and My Friend Flicker (silents), 1971 November 17 - 28 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- Among Our Souvenirs (Hollywood museum), 1971 November 18 - December 5 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- The Monster that Ate Lot 3 (MGM lot 3), 1971 November 30 and December 3 - 12 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      2 drafts
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- Miracle on Vine Street (F. Zegel as Santa Claus) and Citizen Lloyd (Harold Lloyd home), 1971 November 30 and December, 3 - 19; 1972 January 16 (air) (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- Greatest Sell on Earth, 1972 January 9 (air) (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- payment records, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- income and expense recaps, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- legal correspondence and insurance certificate, 1971- 1973 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- program ideas, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - KABC -- Story in Hollywood -- paid bills, 1971 - 1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - KABC -- Ralph Story's AM Show -- rundown sheets and scripts, 1973 September 24 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - KABC -- Ralph Story's AM Show-- rundown sheets and scripts, 1973 September 25 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - KABC -- Ralph Story's AM Show-- rundown sheets and scripts, 1973 September 26 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - KABC -- Ralph Story's AM Show-- rundown sheets and scripts, 1973 September 27 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - KABC -- Ralph Story's AM Show-- rundown sheets and scripts, 1973 September 28 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - KABC -- Ralph Story's AM Show-- publicity, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - KABC -- Ralph Story's AM Show-- program logs, 1974 January 1 - December 31 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - KABC -- Ralph Story's AM Show-- questionnaire, 1973? (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - ABC TV affiliate directory, 1975 April 11 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- New York memos from ABC News production headquarters, 1974 October 29 - 1975 May 23 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Jerry Balme memos, West Coast Production Office, 1974 December 10 - 1975 August 12 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - ABC programming notes, 1974 - 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- broadcast standards and practices and tape screening reports for Ralph Story segments, 1974 December 31 - 1975 August 18 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- broadcast logs for Ralph Story inserts, 1974 January 6 - 1975 August 22 - (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- California state parks permit and letter of reference, 1974 December 12 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Ronald Reagan interview, 1975 January 10 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Roy Rogers interview, 1975 January 10 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Beefalo, 1975 January 14 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- winter vegetables, 1975 January 16 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- winery stories: Mary Ann Graf, Andre Tchelistcheff, Earl Brown, 1975 January 17 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Private backgammon club "Pips" holds invitational tournament for celebrities, 1975 January 17 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Academy Awards preview, 1975 January 22 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- whale watching, 1975 January 23 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Bing Crosby interview, 1975 January 24 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Norman Lear interview, 1975 January 24 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Palm Springs, 1975 January 30 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- "Thinnery" low calorie bakery, 1975 February 7 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Ingrid Bergman interview, 1975 February 7 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- parking lot at Home Savings and Loan paved in "grasscrete", 1975 February 14 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- diet doctor Dr. Mark Saginor, 1975 February 14 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Lily Tomlin interview, 1975 February 21 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Ms. Tall International and tall clubs, 1975 February 21 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Model release agreements for photos by photographer Tim Dressler, 1975 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- SWAT team, 1975 February 24 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Captain Sticky, superhero persona of Richard Pesta, 1975 February 28 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Danny Kaye cooks Chinese food, 1975 February 28 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- inflatable building, the Thomas E. Leavey Activities Center at the University of Santa Clara, 1975 March 7 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- pawn shop in Beverly Hills, 1975 March 7 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- "Golden Hinde II," historian Robert H. Power attempts to recreate voyage of Sir Francis Drake, 1975 March 14 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Joseph Princiotta campaigns to put Alaska on the map, 1975 March 17 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- John Wayne interview, 1975 March 19 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Pie Face International, 1975 March 26 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Oscar night, Academy Awards history, 1975 April 8 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Vietnam orphan adoption, Barbara Brown and family, 1975 April 11 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Academy Award predictions for 1976, 1975 April 11 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Includes press kits for films "Lombard and Gable," "The Hindenburg," "W.C. Fields"
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Titanic anniversary with survivor Edwina Mackenzie and writer Charles Sachs, 1975 April 14 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- youngest mayor, Rusty Hammer of Santa Clara, California, 1975 April 14 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- UCLA basketball coach John Wooden interview, 1975 April 18 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- theater salute with Deborah Kerr and Glynis Johns, 1975 April 18 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- talent search for new Bruce Lee and interview with Linda Lee, widow of Bruce Lee, includes broadcast script, photos, 1975 April 25 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- talent search for new Bruce Lee and interview with Linda Lee, widow of Bruce Lee, includes paperback copy of biography of Bruce Lee written by Linda Lee, 1975 April 25 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Tenth International Tournee of Animation at LACMA, includes paperback copy of book "The Animated Film" by Ralph Stephenson, 1975 May 2 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- treasure hunter and shipwreck excavator Dennis Standefer, 1975 May 7 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Renaissance Pleasure Faire, 1975 May 16 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Tom Hayden and Jane Fonda interviews, 1975 May 30 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- movie review of "The Other Side of the Mountain" and interview with Jill Kinmont, 1975 June 6 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Big Sky, Montana, 1975 June 13 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Beverly Harrell, madam of Nevada brothel, and her Cottontail Ranch, 1975 June 19 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Shark expert Dr. Scott Johnson, 1975 June 20 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Conductor Dr. Antonio Brico, 1975 June 27 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- "General Hospital," behind the scenes of a soap opera, 1975 July 8 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- "Let's Make a Deal" and Monty Hall, 1975 July 10 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Bryna Laub, publisher of Daytime Serial Newsletter, 1975 July 11 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Uri Geller interview, 1975 July 18 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- "School for Country Living", 1975 August 7 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Francis Ford Coppola interview, 1975 August 15 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Christine Wren, woman umpire, 1975 August 22 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Frankenstein wedding, 1975 August 25 - 29 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- cheerleader camp, 1975 August 25 - 29 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Alcatraz, 1975 August 25 - 29 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- "Give 'em Hell, Harry" and actor James Whitmore, 1975 August 25 - 29 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- psychic convention, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- research on stewardesses, the "Rainbow Show", 1975 April (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- research on West Yellowstone, Montana, Milford "Stanley" Poltroon and Wretched Mess News, 1975 May (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- research on Jerry Brown, 1975 January (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- research on religion, 1975 July (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- research on psychiatry, 1975 June (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - CBS "So You Think You Know Los Angeles?" pilot -- scripts for two episodes, shooting schedule, rebroadcast agreement, 1975 March - June (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Movie Minutes -- scripts and other documents for 3 shorts: Do-it-yourself stunts; The first screen kiss; 3-D to holography, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Programming survey -- results of focus group study, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Proposal for series "The Victim Was Unharmed" with Jack Webb, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Ralph Story's Survey Party -- proposal for weekly program, 1976 May (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, ego cars, 1978 January 5 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Lompoc flower festival, 1978 June 20 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- summer solstice, 1978 June 21 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- boat cleaning service "Second Mate", 1978 June 22 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- animal travel agents "Jet Pets", 1978 June 26 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- irrelevant week, 1978 June 27 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --Julie's restaurant, 1978 June 28 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Bob Crane in memoriam, 1978 June 29 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- sundials, 1978 June 29 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Jeanette MacDonald fan club, 1978 June 30 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- tow planes, 1978 July 3 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- decorated house, 1978 July 4 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- movie costume exhibit, Security Pacific Bank art shows, includes photos, program, notes and publicity, 1978 aired July 5 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --Edward R. Murrow biography to announce PBS rebroadcast of "Person-to-person: selected interviews from 1953-1959," includes schedule of interviews to be rebroadcast on PBS, 1978 July 6 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --Lorenzo Music performing at the Icehouse in Pasadena, 1978 July 7 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Dean Jeffries automobile stylist and truck called the "Landmaster" designed for movie Damnation Alley, 1978 July 10 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --Hollywood Bowl 57th season, 1978 July 11 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --bottled water, 1978 July 12 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California Puppet Theater at California Polytechnic State University in San Luis Obispo, 1978 July 13 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Santa Maria BBQ, 1978 July 14 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- "Wrong-Way Corrigan", 1978 July 17 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- "Draw on LA" graffiti art in Santa Monica Pier art show, 1978 June 19 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- art show by students of the Exceptional Children's Foundation Art Center, a center for the mentally retarded and emotionally troubled, 1978 July 18 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Sepulveda dam and reservoir, 1978 July 19 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- watermelon week, 1978 July 20 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California magazine #1, a new feature for Friday broadcasts. Stories include Amazon audition (for movie), China tourism, National Avoid Boredom week, mule races, New Yorker cartoon, 1978 July 21 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- doll museum in Santa Barbara in former bordello, 1978 July 24 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- gift show, 1978 July 26 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Samoan kids tour Western United States to promote tourism, includes color postcards, 1978 July 27 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California magazine #2, 1978 July 28 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      Stories include ocean lifeguard competition, "Test Tube Blues," Kai Haido of Pasadena builds replica of Tara, smog and tooth fillings, 13 year anniversary of cigarette warning, Society for Creative Anachronism, Caltrans wire trees and bumper stickers
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Paul Eagles Circus lunch club, 1978 July 31 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- "Magic Cat" store and mail order business devoted to feline collectibles, 1978 August 1 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- "Quote" magazine, 1978 August 2 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- steel trees (same Caltrans art project as the one mentioned in July 28 California magazine segment), 1978 August 3 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --clown week, 1978 August 4 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --Hollywood sign and Playboy fundraising party, 1978 August 7 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- chigger week (not the bug-- chigger is joke on combination of chuckle and snigger), 1978 August 8 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- restoration of cat faces painted on storm drain flap gates of the Los Angeles River, 1978 August 9 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Great American Shoe Shine Company (shoe shine girls), 1978 August 10 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- home remodeling show, 1978 August 11 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- kiddie hosts, hosts of children's television programs, 1978 August 14 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Chauvin day, birthday of Nicholas Chauvin, 1978 August 15 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- nude statues at the Laguna Beach Sawdust Festival, 1978 August 16 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- weed seeds, 1978 August 17 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- birthday of the potato chip, 1978 August 21 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News calendar for August with notes, 1978 August (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- blimp hangars, 1978 August 22 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- rock band "Mag Wheel and the Lug Nuts," includes cover performance of "Test Tube Blues" (see 1978 July 28 evening news segment), 1978 August 23 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- B-26 bomber, 1978 August 24 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- inventors' fair, 1978 August 25 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --hatpins, 1978 August 28 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --"U-finish" do-it-yourself houses of Golden Hills, 1978 August 29 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- "Renta Yenta" errand and event planning service [see also script in box 57 folder 5], 1978 August 30 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Olympic flashback, 1978 August 31 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- "Invictus" sculpture in Topanga, 1978 August 31 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- World health expo, 1978 September 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Los Angeles birthday, 1978 September 4 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Cuban crocodiles, 1978 September 5 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Charlie Chaplin movies on television, 1978 September 7 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- fish market, dories of Newport Beach, 1978 September 8 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Cookie Post, mailbox business serves cookies, 1978 September 11 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Phonographics, exhibit of album cover art, 1978 September 13 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- calendar adjustment, 1978 September 14 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Los Angeles County fair, 1978 September 15, 18, 20, 21, 22 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- American Living History Theater re-enactment group, 1978 September 19 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- return of Life magazine, 1978 September 25 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- ragtime revival, musicians Jim and Martha Hession, 1978 September 26 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- supermarket art exhibit, 1978 September 27 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- energy fair, 1978 September 28 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1978 September 29 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Ralph Bakshi "The Lord of the Rings," press kit, color slide, 1978 September (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --brass rubbing, 1978 October 3 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- CB birthday, 1978 October 4 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Sweet Adelines women's four part harmony groups, 1978 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1978 October 6 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Oktoberfests, 1978 October 9 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Dodger mascot wannabe Mr. Cool, 1978 October 11 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- National School Lunch Week, 1978 October 12 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1978 October 13 (Box 23, Folder 9)